um this is a different kind of day I
just want to say our hearts go out to
everybody in Charleston South Carolina
right now this this was a horrible uh
story and for those of you who aren't up
to speed here's uh basically what
happened nine people killed in an
unthinkable crime in Charleston South
Carolina before roof opened fire he told
his intended victims I want to shoot
black people he said um you rape our
women and you taken over our country
and you have to go now I have to tell
you guys we weren't uh going to talk
much about this at all I mean seriously
we're a comedy show right I mean what
we've built here isn't really designed
to handle this kind of tragedy and uh
let me just say I know we talk about
race a lot on the show but I think we
can all agree this time that this is a
racially motivated attack you know I
think it's
uh but
also it couldn't be clear when it comes
out of the Killer's mouth right but even
with all of that evidence and on a day
like today Fox News just makes my head
explode well last night's deadly attack
taking place at a historic church in
South Carolina the gunman's horrifying
attack on faith the question is was it a
crime out of race or religion they could
be calling it a hate crime because it
happened in a religious institution so
if we're not safe in our own churches
then where are we safe and although it's
being investigated as a hate crime
there's still some pieces we have to put
together some look at it as well it's
because it was a white guy apparently
and a black church uh but you made a
great point just a moment ago about the
hostility toward Christians so per and
it was a church
okay all right I know you guys don't
want to admit that racial stuff is going
that racial stuff isn't going on but how
can there be any doubt when it came out
out of the gunman's mouth let me remind
you what he said I want to shoot black
people he told his victims I want to
shoot black people I think when he says
black people he means black people and
not
Christians I'm just saying and remember
this part he said um you rape our women
and you taking over our
country and you have to go he is being
very clear nobody thinks Christians are
going around raping everybody and taking
over the country all right that's not a
thing unless you're a Dugger all right
then it's a thing then it's a thing then
it's a thing okay
then and then Fox News sends out a black
preacher like his black is going to
confuse
me right black don't distract uh by the
way right it don't black don't distract
man but but nice try anyway Fox I deeply
concerned that this gunman chose to go
into a church cuz there does seem to be
a rising hostility against Christians
across this country because of our
Biblical views no no no no no it is not
Rising hostility against Christians it's
rising forceful and pervasive hostility
against black people who were meeting in
a church all right but let's hear more
from the fox brother most people jump to
conclusions about race I long for the
day when we stopped doing that in our
country uh but we don't know why he went
into a church but he didn't choose a bar
he didn't choose a basketball court
didn't choose a basketball
court man Oh you mean typically black
areas like basketball courts why didn't
he choose a recording studio I mean he
could have gone to a chitlin Farm I mean
break dancing class roller ranks why
wasn't he had a watermelon stand why did
he go there I mean yeah he could have
and it literally Center could have been
there look if he wanted to Target a high
concentration of black people why didn't
he choose any prison in the United
States why didn't he do that
huh God and it wasn't just Fox News even
GOP Presidential candidate Rick Santorum
couldn't wait to jump on this bandwagon
to wrong town we're now seeing assault
on religious liberty we've never seen
before it's obviously a crime of hate
and we don't know the rationale but I
don't know what what other rationale
could there
be
God what other rationale could there be
I mean for people who live in cut and
dry black and white worlds it's amazing
how social conservatives like Rick
Santorum just stretch and bend and
contort to make sure they never have to
confront race
right I know because look I know because
this was in a church that it's hard to
understand this was about race but let
me give you an example four black girls
were murdered in a church bombing in
Birmingham Alabama in 1963 all right
back then no one pretended to wonder
what the motivation was if you tried to
say it was about religion even the
perpetrators back then would have
corrected
you right no we killed them because
they're
that's why we did
it all right one last thing about this
church is that it has proven itself
resilient for nearly two centuries the
mother Emanuel Church first opened its
doors in 1816 6 years later it was
burned to the ground in 12 12 years
after that all black churches in the
South Carolina were outlawed forcing
mother Emanuel to hold their services in
secret also around that time racist
killed one of the church's co-founders
for planning a slave res a slave revolt
and nearly 200 years later last night
mother emanuel's senior pastor Clemente
Pinkney was added to the list of church
leaders taken from the congregation and
though this is devastating to the church
today it's comforting to know that
mother Emanuel can and will go
on